Hey! I am Christian Burnham Fullstackdeveloper



Full Stack Developer specialized in Front-end development with JavaScript, TypeScript, React, and Node.js. Certified by the Full Stack Open Bootcamp program from the University of Helsinki. I combine technical skills with prior experience in multimedia design to build robust applications focused on user experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

QUINDEV | REMOTO FREE LANCE | AGO 2023 - PRESENT

Full Stack Developer

- Designed and developed reusable React/TypeScript component library
- Integrated Microsoft Power Platform for enterprise process automation
- Performance optimization: Reduced LCP through lazy loading and code splitting
- Currently developing mobile app with React Native & Expo

INSTITUTO DE FOMENTO A LA CREATIVIDAD Y LA INNOVACIÓN FULLTIME | AGO 2023 - PRESENT

Development Analyst

- Technical leadership in the development of Ecuador Film Commission (React + TypeScript + Node.js + MongoDB):
 - Geolocation system for film shooting locations.
 - Front-end design with React, controlled forms using Formik, and validations with Yup.
 - Implemented i18n for English/Spanish support.
 - Designed REST API for front-end integration.
 - Used Material UI components.
 - Documentation with Swagger.
- Development of CinemaEc (React + JavaScript + Node.js + MongoDB):
 - Designed a content gallery with custom components.
 - Created a StoryBook for components.
 - Built REST API for front-end integration.
 - Deployed Firebase Storage.



CONTACTO



Phone: (+593) 987 800 027



attis.alejandro@gmail.com



https://github.com/attisDev92

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/b urnhamchristian92/

EDUCACIÓN

Ingeniería en Producción Audiovisual y Multimedia UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA ISRAEL 2012-2015

Bootcamp Desarrollo Full-StackUNIVERSIDAD DE HELSINKI
2023 - 2024

INSTITUTO DE FOMENTO A LA CREATIVIDAD Y LA INNOVACIÓN FULLTIME | JUN 2020 - AGO 2023

Promotion Analyst

- Online submission system for cultural calls:
 - Designed an informational website (Adobe Muse).
 - Created platform mockups in Figma.
 - Gathered user requirements for the development team.

INSTITUTO DE CINE Y CREACIÓN AUDIOVISUAL | FULLTIME | JUN 2017 - JUN 2020

Communication Analyst

- Created motion graphics (After Effects), optimizing content for different websites.
- Designed social media graphics (Facebook & Instagram).
- Managed WordPress websites.

FEATURED PROJECTS _____

Ecuador Film Commission

https://ecuadorfilmcommission.com/

- Stack: React, Node.js, MongoDB, Mapbox GL, Redux
- Bilingual platform for promoting Ecuador's film industry.
- · Geolocation-based search.
- · Controlled forms.
- Content creation and role-based user management.
- REST API with Node.js & Express, documented with Swagger.

CinemaEC

https://cinemaec.com/

- Stack: React, Firebase, Material UI
- Catalog of Ecuadorian films with digital rights management.
- · JWT authentication and custom roles.
- Cloud file handling with Firebase Storage.
- · Component library with StoryBook.

EndureceRun (En desarrollo)

https://github.com/attisDev92/run-bike-app-API

- Backend development for a mobile app.
- NestJS, REST API & GraphQL.
- Module and service creation.
- Documentation with Swagger.
- Integration with PostgreSQL & TypeORM.

COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS

- Project Management with
 Agile & Lean Methodologies –
 Telefónica Foundation
- Full-Stack GraphQL
 Development University of Helsinki
- GraphQL, Apollo Client & Apollo Server for Frontend & Backend – University of Helsinki
- Programming Fundamentals LinkedIn

TECHNOLOGIES & TOOLS

- UI Desing (Figma, Penpot)
- Github y Git
- VSCode, Cursor
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- React, React Native, Expo
- NodeJS, Express, NestJS
- GraphQL
- Redux, ReactQuery
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- HTML5, CSS3, CSS
 Modules, Material UI, React Bootstrap
- Firebase, Render, Netlify
- IA (Github Copilot, Cloude Sonet, Ulzard,)

Referencias

- Samantha Chimborazo
- Digital Marketing Director, Progress Group
- 0939689010

José Carvajal

- CTO QuinDev & SIMED
- 0982230654

Patricia Flores

- Technical General Coordinator, Institute for Creativity & Innovation
- 0995073261